🎵 10,000 Reasons (송축해 내 영혼) - 찬양 전주
10,000 Reasons - Matt Redman (Intro)
[후렴] 송축해 내 영혼, 내 영혼아, 거룩하신 주의 이름
Bless the Lord, O my soul, O my soul, Worship His holy name
이전에 없던 노래로, 주님을 찬양해
Sing like never before, O my soul, I'll worship Your holy name
[1절] 해가 뜨는 새 아침 밝았네, 이제 다시 주를 노래할 시간
The sun comes up, it's a new day dawning, It's time to sing Your song again
무슨 일이 내게 닥쳐와도, 저녁이 올 때까지 찬양하리라
Whatever may pass and whatever lies before me, Let me be singing when the evening comes
[후렴] 송축해 내 영혼, 내 영혼아, 거룩하신 주의 이름
Bless the Lord, O my soul, O my soul, Worship His holy name
이전에 없던 노래로, 주님을 찬양해
Sing like never before, O my soul, I'll worship Your holy name
[2절] 주는 자비롭고 노하기를 더디하시며, 주는 위대하고 온유하시네
You're rich in love and You're slow to anger, Your name is great and Your heart is kind
주의 모든 선하심을 노래하리, 내 마음이 발견한 만 가지 이유로
For all Your goodness I will keep on singing, Ten thousand reasons for my heart to find
[후렴] 송축해 내 영혼, 내 영혼아, 거룩하신 주의 이름
Bless the Lord, O my soul, O my soul, Worship His holy name
이전에 없던 노래로, 주님을 찬양해
Sing like never before, O my soul, I'll worship Your holy name
[3절] 내 힘이 다하고 그 날이 이를 때, 주를 찬양하는 내 영혼의 노래는 끝나지 않으리
And on that day when my strength is failing, The end draws near and my time has come, Still my soul will sing Your praise unending
영원토록, 만 년이 지나도 영원토록 찬양하리라
Ten thousand years and then forevermore, Forevermore
[후렴 절정] 송축해 내 영혼, 내 영혼아, 거룩하신 주의 이름을 경배해!
Bless the Lord, O my soul, worship His holy name! Sing like never before!
거룩하신 주의 이름을 영원히 경배하리라
Yes, I will worship Your holy name, Lord, I'll worship Your holy name
🕊️ 만 가지 이유로 주님을 영원히 송축합니다 · 아멘
Praising the Lord with 10,000 Reasons Forever · Amen